chestpubs.org 2014-05-19

# CHEST Publications | Privacy Policy

Tracking Activity  
Personal Information  
Security

* * *

## **Tracking Activity **

Cookies. This website may store some information on the hard drive of a user’s computer in the form of a "cookie." A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a browser from a server and stored on the user’s hard drive. These cookies are intended to improve the ease of use of the site by remembering usernames, identifying user preferences, tracking click streams, and for load balancing. These cookies enable faster service, updated results, and a more personalized site experience. All browsers can be set to reject the use of cookies. However, doing this may hinder performance online. [Users can click here to learn more about adjusting browser settings.](http://www.google.com/support/websearch/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=35851)

Log Files. Log files are used to collect general data about the movement of visitors through our site and digital applications. This may include some or all of the following information: the Internet Protocol Address (IP Address) of a user’s computer or other digital device, host name, domain name, browser version and platform, date and time of requests, and the files downloaded or viewed. This information is used to measure and analyze traffic and performance of the offerings and features on the site.

* * *

## **Personal Information**

**Collection**  
From General, Anonymous Users. When users browse this website without logging in through a personal or institutional subscription, they browse anonymously. Personally identifiable information--such as name, address, phone number, and e-mail address--is not collected or accessible. Aggregate data, such as the number of hits per page, is collected and used to measure and analyze traffic and performance of the offerings and features on the site.

From Registered Users and Subscribers. When a person becomes a registered user on this site, or chooses to interact with this site in other ways, such as purchasing a product, requesting e-mail alerts, or using the “Contact Us” form, certain personal information is collected. Credit card numbers are not stored in the system.

**Use**  
Information provided online is used to process, fulfill, and deliver requests for content and services. If a user has not opted-out of receiving marketing communications, their e-mail address may be used on occasion to alert them to new products or services that may be of interest. Users may opt-out of e-mail alerts at any time.

Deidentified aggregate usage information, which may include demographic data, may be reported to third parties, including our third-party vendors and advertisers.

**Sharing**  
Personally identifying information, such as names and contact information, of subscribers and site registrants is not shared or made available for purchase to outside organizations or companies. American College of Chest Physician member information may be available through the organization's membership list.

It may be necessary to share personal information with third-party companies with whom CHEST contracts to perform work related to the maintenance of the website, consulting, marketing, and other services, but such partners are prohibited from using the information provided for any other purpose.

The organization may disclose personally identifying information if required to do so by law or in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or legal process; (2) protect our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or the unauthorized use of our website; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public. 

**Retention**  
Personal information on customers is retained as dictated by business and legal requirements.

* * *

## **Security**

Safeguards, including use of sophisticated encryption and authentication tools, are used to ensure the security of personal information. Information collected is stored in secure environments and appropriate precautions are taken to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of that information.

**Children Under 13**  
We do not knowingly solicit data online from, or market online, to children under the age of 13.

THIS PRIVACY POLICY MAY BE CHANGED AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE.
